# Maxwell A. Handler

Mhandler1991@gmail.com • (650) 759-2961 • 6520 Beadnell Way 1-L, San Diego, CA 92117

#### Salesforce Certified Administrator

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Motivated and strategically-minded Salesforce Administration expert capable of working independently and part of a diverse team to build stable and customized salesforce.com environments. Amicable professional with a wide array of experience in multiple instances of Salesforce. Organized and able to translate organizational, departmental, and user needs into sustainable declarative systematic solutions. Experience assisting and training users with a wide-array of knowledge within Salesforce. Eager and persistent employee constantly striving to expand personal knowledge and experience.

#### **SKILLS**

Sales & Service Cloud, Profiles, Roles, Workflow Rules, Process Builders, Flows, VisualForce Pages, Actions, Buttons, Reports, Dashboards, Custom Objects, Custom Fields, Data Loader, Assignment Rules, Customer/Partner Community, Lightning, Mobile, Communication Templates, CPQ, Validation Rules, Approval Processes, Layouts, Custom Permission, Permission Sets System Knowledge: Gainsight, Hubspot, Eloqua, Advologix, Apttus, Conga, Marketo

**Certifications:** Salesforce Certified Administrator

### WORK EXPERIENCE

Salesforce Administrator, Ambry Genetics, Aliso Viejo, CA

April 2018 - Present

- Salesforce administrator & subject matter expert managing Sales & Service Cloud with 250+ Users
- Implement Sales Cloud, Service Cloud & all internal business units
- Assist in establishing bi-directional communication between Salesforce & internal databases
- Develop sales & forecasting processes in relation to Salesforce
- Train & on-board new users and provide ongoing training to Salesforce users
- Advise is prioritization of Salesforce projects along with the procedural and systematic impacts
- Maintain data security to comply with HIPPA regulations

#### Senior Business Analyst, Ceridian, Virtual

October 2016 - April 2018

- Sole Salesforce administrator & subject matter expert managing 800+ global users
- Responsible for designing, configuring, testing, training, documenting and deploying SFDC functionality
- Develop and deploy Salesforce Lightning & Salesforce1 customization
- Liaison between 45 business departments including sales, marketing, and legal
- Assist with management of 3rd party packages including Eloqua, Advologix, Apttus, SF CPQ, & Conga
- Create and update custom declarative solutions including workflows, process builders, flows, custom buttons, & visualforce pages

## Sales and Operations Analyst, Clarus Designs, San Francisco, CA

August 2015 - September 2016

- Advise companies on data analytics, internal structure, systematic & organizational processes, and implemented technologies.
- Create profiles and role hierarchy for users to ensure accurate security settings within Salesforce
- Analyze business system solutions and processes in order to streamline and create more user efficient environments
- Train and support end users with 3rd party solutions including Salesforce, Marketo, and Hubspot
- Develop extensive reports and dashboards to improve visibility for end users

## **PROJECTS**

## **Component Management**

An installed package designed specifically for Salesforce development documentation. Component Management is a declarative package that aligns salesforce configuration and customization to business processes, cases, and stakeholders. This ensures stability while creating a historical repository of the environments evolution. Reporting within this package gives understanding into critical details in how the system is tied together through related cases and changes.

## **EDUCATION**

B.A., Sociology, Law and Society, University of California, Riverside

June 2014

Full Stack Developer Certification, University of California, San Diego

December 2020